Upton Sinclair Miscellaneous Materials VII: Articles about Sinclair and His Works, 1906-1965 PS3537.I85 (InU-Li-VAE1864)
Lilly Library
- Graf Keyserling in Amerika? (In Der Fackelreiter. Hamburg. Nr. 5, Mai 1928. p. 236) Criticizing Sinclair's comments on Keyserling., PS3537.I85 Z684 (Box No Box)
- Grierson, Francis, 1848–1927. The symposium on endowment. (In The new age. Aug. 4, 1910. p. 320–321) An answer to Sinclair's plea for the endowment of young writers., PS3537.I85 Z6846 (Box No Box)
- Gruening, Ernest, 1887–1974. What every newspaperman knows: The brass check, a study of American journalism. (In The nation. v. 3, no. 2872, July 17, 1920. p. 72–73) A review, signed at end: Ernest H. Gruening., PS3537.I85 Z6853 (Box No Box)
- H.,B. America's prohibition experiment: prohibitionist to the attack, Sinclair's "Wet parade" / (by "B. H.") (In Barrier daily truth. Broken Hill. June 14, 1932), PS3537.I85 Z6855 (Box No Box)
- Haldeman–Julius, E. (Emanuel), 1888–1951. The haters of Upton Sinclair / by E. Haldeman–Julius. (In The Haldeman–Julius weekly. Girard, Kan. no. 1659, Sept. 17, 1927. p. 2–4), PS3537.I85 Z686 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Hansen, Harry, 1884– The first reader: old Upton Sinclair. (From The New York World. July 15, 1927) Includes a review of Floyd Dell's "Upton Sinclair.", PS3537.I85 Z6874 (Box No Box)
- Hansen, Harry, 1884– Upton Sinclair letters tell much about others / by Harry Hanson. (From an unidentified newspaper. 1 p.: port.) A review of "My lifetime in letters.", PS3537.I85 Z6876 (Box No Box)
- Harris, Frank, 1855–1931. Lincoln libeled by Upton Sinclair. (From Pearson's magazine. July 1919. P. 395–396) Includes Sinclair's answer to the charge made by Harris., PS3537.I85 Z688 (Box No Box)
- Hawthorne in solitude and Sinclair in social protest. (From The New York evening sun, The book column. July 28, 1927. 1 p.) Review of Floyd Dell's "Upton Sinclair.", PS3537.I85 Z691 (Box No Box)
- Heart wife in Bermuda Saturday. (From The New York evening journal. Dec. 31, 1913. 1 p.) Concerning a friend of the Sinclairs., PS3537.I85 Z6923 (Box No Box)
- Helm, Morris. Three questions for Upton Sinclair. (In Pacific weekly. Apr. 13, 1936. p. 198–199), PS3537.I85 Z6924 (Box No Box)
- Herreshoff, David. Upton Sinclair's "Jungle" / by David Herreshoff. (In The American Socialist. v. 3, no. 11, Nov. 1956. p. 15–16: ill.), PS3537.I85 Z69245 (Box No Box)
- Hicks, Granville, 1901–1982. War makers and peacemakers. (In The new republic. June 24, 1940. p. 863) A review of "World's end" by U. Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z69247 (Box No Box)
- Holmes, John Haynes, 1879–1964. I, candidate for governor, and how I got licked / review by Rev. John Haynes Holmes ... [in] "Unity" March 18, 1935. [Pasadena, Calif.: U. Sinclair], 1936. [3] p.; 8vo. Brochure includes a plea by Sinclair for purchases of the book; and a review of the book from the London "Times" Feb. 21, 1935., PS3537.I85 Z6925 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Holmes, John Haynes, 1879–1964. A modern prophet. (In Unity. July 24, 1933. p. 305), PS3537.I85 Z6926 (Box No Box)
- Holmes, John Haynes, 1879–1964. A novel of living together, Co–op, by Upton Sinclair. (In Unity. Feb. 1, 1937. p. 215–216) Book review., PS3537.I85 Z6927 (Box No Box)
- Holmes, John Haynes, 1879–1964. Through Gentile eyes / by John Haynes Holmes. [New York: U. Sinclair], 1942. [4] p.; 8vo. From "Opinion," New York, April 1942. A discussion of Sinclair's newly published Dragon's teeth. Includes other opinions of the book., PS3537.I85 Z69272 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Hope of world is in youth — Sinclair: author speaks to audience of 2,000 at gym last night. (In The capital times. Madison, Wisc., [s.d.]), PS3537.I85 Z6928 2 copies (Box No Box)
- How Sinclair knows the smart set. (From The literary digest. May 9, 1908. p. 687–688: port.), PS3537.I85 Z693 (Box No Box)
- Humm, Rudolf Jakob, 1985– Upton Sinclair, Co–op: der Weg der amerikanischen Arbeitslosen zur Selbsthilife — Büchergilde Gutenberg. [Zurich, 1936] 1 p. (Der öffentliche Dienst) Signed at end: R.J. Humm. Contains also: Unterredung mit Präsident Roosevelt; aus Co–op von Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z6934 (Box No Box)
- Humm, Rudolf Jakob, 1895– Upton Sinclair und sein neuestes Buch, Co–op / von R.J. Humm. (In Büchergilde Zürich. Heft 7, Juli 1937. p. 102–106: ill.), PS3537.I85 Z6937 (Box No Box)
- Hurwitz, Maxmillian. As Gentiles see it / by Maxmillian Hurwitz. (From Jewish Tribune. New York. May 28, 1926) Third and last part of Hurwitz' review of Judenhass: eine Anthologie, in which he attacks Sinclair's contribution to that work., PS3537.I85 Z6938 2 copies (Box No Box)
- In defense of the "Muck–raker" (From The literary digest. Sept. 19, 1908.), PS3537.I85 Z694 (Box No Box)
- Ingenious effects obtained in play. (In Pasadena star–news. Apr. 1925) New item concerning "The pot boiler" by Upton Sinclair, currently playing at the Savoy Theatre., PS3537.I85 Z6944 (Box No Box)
- International rollo. (In Time magazine. Mar. 24, 1941. p. 90) Book review of Sinclair's Between two worlds., PS3537.I85 Z6946 (Box No Box)
- An interview with Upton Sinclair, candidate for governor. (In Dune forum. 1934. p. 91–92), PS3537.I85 Z6948 (Box No Box)
- Jail Upton Sinclair, is demand of Oaks: author is carried to mystery cell by chief of police. (From Los Angeles express. Los Angeles. v. 53, no. 44, May 16, 1923. 1 p.) A news report., PS3537.I85 Z697 (Box No Box)
- The Bulletin of the Jewish Center, v. 6, no. 7, Nov. 11, 1927. Cleveland: Jewish Center, 1927. [4] p.; 8vo. Contains (p. [4]) an announcement that "Upton Sinclair will speak at our first forum ... on Does money control life." Article about Sinclair, p. [3]., PS3537.I85 Z6973 (Box No Box)
- Jonson, Jack. Dzhunglu. (In Izvestia. June 30–July 6, 1963. p. 6–7), PS3537.I85 Z6974 (Box No Box)
- Jung, C. G. (Carl Gustav), 1875–1961. The challenge of the Christian enigma: a letter from C.G. Jung to Upton Sinclair. (In New republic. Apr. 27, 1953. p. 18–19) Concerning Sinclair's book "A personal Jesus.", PS3537.I85 Z6975 2 copies (Box No Box)
- 'Jungle' author greets union. ( In The packinghouse worker. v. 18, no. 9, Oct. 1958. p. 4), PS3537.I85 Z69754 (Box No Box)
- Karsner, David, 1889–1941. Upton Sinclair / by David Karsner. (In Art review. July 1922. p. 10, 24–25) Signed by author at end of article., PS3537.I85 Z698 (Box No Box)
- Kimbrough, Hunter. Chief Oaks — you are subpoenaed / by Hunter Kimbrough. (In The call magazine. New York. July 1, 1923. p. [1], section 2) Concerns the arrest of Upton Sinclair, himself and others in Los Angeles., PS3537.I85 Z6983 (Box No Box)
- Kimbrough, Hunter. "Cut out that Constitution stuff" / by Hunter Kimbrough. (From The Haldeman–Julius weekly. Girard, Kan. 1923. 1 p.) Refers to the arrest of Kimbrough, Upton Sinclair and others in Los Angeles., PS3537.I85 Z6985 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Kimbrough, Hunter. Theirs be the guilt, by Upton Sinclair ... / reviewed by Hunter S. Kimbrough. (In The Dixie guide. Gulfport, Miss. v. 36, no. 1, Jan. 1960. p. 2), PS3537.I85 Z69853 (Box No Box)
- King Coal, by Upton Sinclair. (In The nation. Oct. 11, 1917. p. 403–[405]) Book review., PS3537.I85 Z6986 (Box No Box)
- Kisch, Egon Erwin, 1885–1948. Egon Erwin Kisch gespräch mit Upton Sinclair: er erzählt von John Reed, Sacco und Vanzetti, von Rosa Luxemburg und Karl Liebknecht, von Walther Rathenau, von Chaplin und Fairbanks, von der Farm Jack Londons und von der Prohibition. (In Die neue Bücherschau. Berlin. v. 7, no. 7, Juli 1929. p. 349–353), PS3537.I85 Z6988 (Box No Box)
- Laidler, Harry Wellington, 1884–1970. L.I.D. [League for Industrial Democracy] prepares for fortieth anniversary. (In L.I.D. newsbulletin. v. 9, no. 4, Oct. 1944. p. 1–2: port.) The League for Industrial Democracy was founded by Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z704 (Box No Box)
- Laidler, Harry Wellington, 1884–1970. Upton Sinclair, pioneer and molder of an era / by Dr. Harry W. Laidler. (In The workmen's circle call. Nov. 1958. p. 5–6), PS3537.I85 Z705 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Lapin, Adam. Upton Sinclair — pioneer. (From Frontiers. 1930. p. 9–10: port.) Signed at end: Adam Lapin., PS3537.I85 Z71 (Box No Box)
- Lee, Charles, 1913– More about Superbudd ... / by Charles Lee. (In Saturday review. Apr. 18, 1953. p. 23, 41) A review of Sinclair's "The return of Lanny Budd.", PS3537.I85 Z713 (Box No Box)
- Lippmann, Walter, 1889–1974. Upton Sinclair / by Walter Lippman. (From The Saturday review of literature. v. 4, no. 32, Mar. 3, 1928. p. [1–2]) A review of F. Dell's Upton Sinclair: a study in social protest., PS3537.I85 Z72 (Box No Box)
- Logan, Robert Restalrig. The brass check. (In The starry cross; formerly Journal of zoöphily. Philadelphia. v. 29, no. 6, June 1920. p. [83]–84) A review, signed at end: R.R.L., PS3537.I85 Z7205 (Box No Box)
- M., D. "Money writes" in South Africa: a review of Upton Sinclair's book on present–day American literature from the "Cape Times", Cape Town, South Africa, in black verse. (From New era. Los Angeles. Dec. 1, 1931), PS3537.I85 Z721 (Box No Box)
- MacKendrick, Alexander. King Coal, by Upton Sinclair. (From The public. Nov. 23, 1917. p. 1136) Book review., PS3537.I85 Z7213 (Box No Box)
- McWilliams, Carey. Strange case of Upton Sinclair / by Carey McWilliams. (In Pacific weekly. Feb. 3, 1936. p. 53–55), PS3537.I85 Z7214 (Box No Box)
- Macy, John Albert, 1877–1932. Sinclair revealed and Hawthorne obscured / by John Macy. (In The bookman. Oct. 1927. p. 216–218) In part, a review of "Upton Sinclair: a study in social protest" by Floyd Dell., PS3537.I85 Z7215 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Major and minor. (In Musical leader. Chicago. July 18, 1918) Brief comment on Sinclair's "Jungle.", PS3537.I85 Z722 (Box No Box)
- Martin, Doris N. Sacrifice. (In The daily Athenaeum: the student newspaper of West Virginia University. Morgantown, W.V. v. 68, no. 119, Apr. 21, 1956. p. 2) A review of Sinclair's "The cup of fury." Signed at end: D.N.M. (Full name supplied by U. Sinclair.), PS3537.I85 Z7225 (Box No Box)
- Mason, Bruce Bonner. After two decades: a look back at Upton Sinclair's E.P.I.C. scheme / by Bruce B. Mason. (In Frontier. Aug. 1955. p. 12–13), PS3537.I85 Z7228 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880–1956. The goslings, by Upton Sinclair ... / reviewed by H.L. Mencken. (From an unidentified Baltimore newspaper), PS3537.I85 Z723 (Box No Box)
- Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880–1956. On journalism / by H.L. Mencken. (From an unidentified periodical. 138–144 p.) An answer to Sinclair's "The brass check.", PS3537.I85 Z7232 (Box No Box)
- "Mental Radio" [London, 1930] 1 leaf; 14 x 31 cm. Reprint from the London "Times" literary supplement, Thurs., July 3, 1930; in double columns. A review of Upton Sinclair's "Mental radio: does it work and how?", PS3537.I85 Z72325 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Ein merkwürdiger Kampf gegen die Zensur. (From Berliner illustrirte Zeitung. 36 Jahrg., Nr. 35, Aug. 28, 1927. p. [1385]) Full page photograph of Upton Sinclair on a street in Baltimore with placard: Oil! Fig leaf edition., PS3537.I85 Z7233 (Box No Box)
- The millennium: book review / by Card No. 794514. (From Industrial pioneer. Jan. 1925. p. 32–34), PS3537.I85 Z7234 (Box No Box)
- Mrs. Sinclair engaged: divorced Wife of novelist to wed man she met in a sanitarium. (From New York Times. June 16, 1931) News item concerning the announcement of the engagement of the first Mrs. Sinclair and Hughbert Halliwell., PS3537.I85 Z7236 (Box No Box)
- Mr. Upton Sinclair and "Money writes" (From Public opinion. Aug. 7, 1931. p. 134.) Includes a brief review of "Money writes" and Sinclair's opinions on the ways of the idle rich., PS3537.I85 Z724 (Box No Box)
- Molasses & Manassas. (In Time magazine. Dec. 21, 1959) Review of "Theirs be the guilt.", PS3537.I85 Z725 (Box No Box)
- Moley, Raymond, 1886–1975. Looking backward with Mr. Sinclair and Mr. Hoover. (In Today. v. 2, no. 24, Oct. 6, 1934. p. 12–13) Article signed at end: Raymond Moley. Contains also Can Sinclair win? / by Webb Waldron., PS3537.I85 Z726 (Box No Box)
- Mondadori, Arnoldo. Upton Sinclair. [S.l.: s.n., s.d.] 1 leaf; 11 x 16 cm., PS3537.I85 Z728 (Box No Box)
- Morris, Lawrence S. (Lawrence Shackelford), b. 1894. Upton Sinclair: the way of a reformer. (In The new republic. Mar. 7 1928. p. 90–93), PS3537.I85 Z733 (Box No Box)
- Moscow attacks Upton Sinclair: literary critic brands American novelist 'moneygrubbing' Wall Street propagandist. (From Los Angeles Times. Apr. 21, 1949), PS3537.I85 Z735 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Murray, Helen Grace. The man who has kept the faith: Upton Sinclair / Helen Grace Murray. (In Zion's herald. Boston. v. 107, no. 25, June 19, 1929. p. 778: port.), PS3537.I85 Z74 (Box No Box)
- Music, dramatic and allied arts under EPIC. [Los Angeles, 1934] [4] p.; 8vo. A proposal for aid to creative artists under Sinclair's EPIC plan; endorsed by Sinclair in note at end., PS3537.I85 Z742 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Nesbit, Wilbur D. (Wilbur Dick), 1871–1927. " The muck–rakers." (From The independent. May 24, 1906) Poem, signed W.D. Nesbit., PS3537.I85 Z743 (Box No Box)
- New Books / edited by The Gadfly. (From The young worker. Nov. 15, 1906) Review of "The jungle.", PS3537.I85 Z7432 (Box No Box)
- [News item concerning the play "Prince Hagen" which will be played for the first time on any stage at Valencia Theatre] (From The San Francisco Call. Jan. 9, 1909), PS3537.I85 Z7434 1909 (Box No Box)
- [News item concerning the play "Prince Hagen", currently being played at the Valencia Theatre] (From The Argonaut. San Francisco. Jan. 16, 1909), PS3537.I85 Z7434 1909a (Box No Box)
- [News item concering the production of " Prince Hagen." (From Show world. San Francisco. Jan. 23, 1909), PS3537.I85 Z7434 1909b (Box No Box)
- O'Brien, Frederick. Upton Sinclair: the man and his books / by Frederick O'Brien. (In The daily Carmelite. Carmel, Calif. July 28, 1931), PS3537.I85 Z745 (Box No Box)
- Olsson, Oscar, 1877–1950. Leo Tolstoj och Upton Sinclair: 100 år och 50 år. (In Bokstungan: studiecirklarnas tidskrift. arg. 12, nr. 8, Oct. 1928. p. [229]–232), PS3537.I85 Z747 (Box No Box)
- Once more, book of the month is The jungle. (In Book collecting. San Francisco. v. 5, no. 9, [1934] p. 7) Included is a notice [p. 6] of a bibliography of Upton Sinclair, by Mrs. Stone, Librarian of Felton Memorial Library at Stanford University., PS3537.I85 Z7473 (Box No Box)
- Other strings to their bows. (In Vanity fair. Oct. 1932. p. 22) Among the portraits of famous people who play the violin, is that of Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z7496 (Box No Box)
- Our cover boy. (In Rob Wagner's Script. v. 29, no. 5, May 29, 1943. p. 10–11) Portrait of Upton Sinclair on cover., PS3537.I85 Z74964 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Padmanabhan Tampy, K.P. Upton Sinclair / by K.P. Padmanabhan Tampy. (In Landholders' journal. Oct. 1938. p. [37]–41: port.), PS3537.I85 Z7497 1938 (Box No Box)
- Panorama. Praha, 1928 1 no. illus., ports. An Upton Sinclair number. In pictorial paper wrappers, with portrait of Sinclair on cover., PS3537.I85 Z75 (Box No Box)
- Paperbacks in review: fiction reprints. (From New York Times book review. Dec. 10, 1961. p. 50) Included in the list is Upton Sinclair's "Dragon's teeth.", PS3537.I85 Z752 (Box No Box)
- Pedeck, Albert Adam. Upton Sinclair. (In Contact: maandblad voor de Nederlandse jeugd. Nov. 15, 1939. p. 417–419; port.), PS3537.I85 Z759 (Box No Box)
- The "Persecution complex." (From The Minneapolis Sunday tribune. July 2, 1922. p. 2) An editorial. In hand of Sinclair in margin: Pretty thin stuff — gossamer., PS3537.I85 Z762 (Box No Box)
- Petit, Georges. Upton Sinclair — la cite des Anges. (In Le revue nouvelle. v. 5, no. 50, Sept. 1929. p. 117–118) Review of "They call Me Carpenter.", PS3537.I85 Z7624 (Box No Box)
- Phelps, William Lyon, 1865–1943. As I like it / by William Lyon Phelps. (In an unidentified magazine. Nov. 1924. p. 554–560) Among the authors discussed is Upton Sinclair and his article in The Independent, June 19, 1902, "Language study: some facts.", PS3537.I85 Z7626 (Box No Box)
- Photograph of writer benefits the barbers. (From The San Francisco call. Jan. 11, 1909) A press clipping, in which Sinclair's diet and hair are ridiculed., PS3537.I85 Z763 (Box No Box)
- Poritzky, J. E. (Jakob Elias), 1876–1935. Petroleum, von Upton Sinclair. (In Weltstimmen. Stuttgart. Heft 7, Sept. 1928. p. [247]–251: ill., port.) A review of Sinclair's Oil!, PS3537.I85 Z764 (Box No Box)
- Poulaille, Henry. Upton Sinclair, a propos du "Pétrole." (From Le Peuple. Paris. Apr. 30, 1928) At head of title: Les grands escrivains du monde., PS3537.I85 Z766 (Box No Box)
- Prodding the Nobel Prize committee: a symposium. (In Books abroad. 1931. p. 372–376) Concerning the campaign of Sinclair for the Nobel prize., PS3537.I85 Z768 (Box No Box)
- A prophet of castastrophe: Upton Sinclair and hell fire. (In Readers news. London. v. 3, no. 4, Sept. 1940. p. [37]–38: port.), PS3537.I85 Z769 (Box No Box)
- Raffé, W. G. (Walter George), b. 1888. Upton Sinclair: his books and plays / by W.G.R. (From The Hindustan review. Calcutta. Oct. 1927. p. 14–18), PS3537.I85 Z773 (Box No Box)
- Randall, A. E. (Alfred Edward), 1862–1925. The endowment of genius: a rejoiner / by Alfred E. Randall. (In The new age. June 23, 1910. p. 178–179) An answer to Sinclair's plea for "The endowment of genius.", PS3537.I85 Z774 (Box No Box)
- Ratcliffe, S. K. (Samuel Kerkham), 1868–1958. A man with a mission / by S.K. Ratcliffe. (In John O'London's weekly. v. 1, no. 1, 227, Feb. 25, 1944. p. 1–2: port.), PS3537.I85 Z7744 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Read, Herbert Edward, Sir, 1893–1968. A man without art. (In The new English weekly. Nov. 1, 1934. p. 57–59) A review of Sinclair's "Mammonart." Signed at end: Herbert Read., PS3537.I85 Z775 (Box No Box)
- Recent fiction and the critics. (In Current Literature. 1908. p. [569]–570) Review of Sinclair's "The metropolis.", PS3537.I85 Z776 (Box No Box)
- Renaud, Ralph E. Upton Sinclair descants on the stage socialistic. (From The bulletin. San Francisco. v. 107, no. 75, Jan. 2, 1909. p. [1] feature section: ill.), PS3537.I85 Z78 (Box No Box)
- R–R–Revenge!: Brown sends Arden foes to the stone pile. ( From The North American. Philadelphia. Aug. 2, 1911. p. 1, 5: ill., ports.), PS3537.I85 Z781 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858–1919. [Two personal letters to Upton Sinclair, dated Washington, April 11, 1906 and March 15, 1906.] 5 p. Photostat copies (negative) from the Roosevelt manuscripts., PS3537.I85 Z7815 (Box No Box)
- Rosenhouse, Bernard. Interview Sinclair, famed author: gives views on business depression. (In Rough ride. Roosevelt High School, Los Angeles. v. 15, no. 12, Dec. 11, 1930. p. 1, 4), PS3537.I85 Z782 (Box No Box)
- Rudens, S.P. Love and society. (From East and west magazine. July 21, 1922) Review of Sinclair's The Book of life., PS3537.I85 Z785 (Box No Box)
- Rygh, George Taylor, 1860–1942. Critique of noteworthy books / Georg Taylor Rygh; The brass check, A study of American journalism, by Upton Sinclair. (In American Lutheran survey. Sept. 1920. p. 38–39), PS3537.I85 Z788 (Box No Box)
- S., P.J. Jimmie Higgins. (In The new justice. v. 1, no. 9, June 15, 1919. p. 14) Signed at end: P.J.S. On back cover of periodical is an advertisement for the novel, Jimmie Higgins., PS3537.I85 Z79 (Box No Box)
- Salpeter, Harry. Mammonart, by Upton Sinclair. (In an unidentified periodical. [1925] p. 236–38) A review., PS3537.I85 Z791 (Box No Box)
- "Samuel The Seeker." (In The sketch. London. July 6, 1910) A review of the book., PS3537.I85 Z792 (Box No Box)
- Sandburg, Carl, 1878–1967. From the notebook of Carl Sandburg. (From The Chicago daily news. Sept. 7, 1927) On verso of this clipping is: Poet and propagandist / by Etta S. Preston., PS3537.I85 Z7922 (Box No Box)
- Sceptical musings and distrust greet Sinclair's advocary of "Epic" plan. (In Call of youth. New York. v. 1, no. 11, Nov. 1933. p. [1], 7), PS3537.I85 Z79254 (Box No Box)
- Der Schriftsteller des socialen Kampes: Upton Sinclair. (In Magazin der Bücher. Berlin. 1929–30. p. 4–5: port.) Unsigned article., PS3537.I85 Z7926 (Box No Box)
- Senn, Paul. Besuch bei Upton Sincliar: unser reporter Paul Senn suchte auf seiner letztjährigen Amerkareise den berühmten Schriftsteller in seinem Heim in der Nähe von Los Angeles auf. (In Sie und er. 21 März 1947. p. 36: ill., port.), PS3537.I85 Z79264 (Box No Box)
- Sharp, R.V. Literature is a field of hard labor / by R.V. Sharp. (In Border cities star. Windsor, Ont. June 10, 1927), PS3537.I85 Z7927 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair, Mary Craig. Beware my dog!: warning from the wife of a friend of mankind. (In The new republic. v. 65, no. 709, July 4, 1928. Back cover), PS3537.I85 Z793 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair, Mary Craig. Is this book obscene?: a few words from Upton Sinclair's wife concerning "Oil." [Long Beach, Calif., 1927] [4] p.; 8vo., PS3537.I85 Z794 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Sinclair, Mary Craig. Marx and Sinclair. (In The New York Times book review. May 31, 1953) Letter to the editor., PS3537.I85 Z7943 2 copies (Box No Box)
- A Socialist and Sinclair. (In Pearson's magazine. Nov. 1917. p. [219]–221) An anonymous letter to Sinclair, together with his reply [p. 221]., PS3537.I85 Z795 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1878–1968, defendant ... The people of the State of New York on the complaint of Frank G. Wilson, against Upton Sinclair and others. Opinion. [New York, 1914] 19ࡁ. 26.8cm. At head cover title: Court of general sessions of the peace, New York County. Brief affirming the judgment against Sinclair and other for picketing the office of John D. Rockefeller in New York, dated 7 July 1914. From the library of Upton Sinclair. In paper cover., PS3537.I85 Z82 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1878–1968. [Scrapbook of portraits taken at the wedding of Upton Sinclair and Mary Elizabeth (Hard) Willis, in 1961.] 24 photgraphs. 34 cm. In red plastic covers. A gift from Life Bureau Chief, Richard B Stolley., PS3537.I85 Z823 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair Bureau, San Francisco. The Sinclair players: results of opening performances. San Francisco, [ca. 1909] 1 leaf: 34 x 21 cm., PS3537.I85 Z8302 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair attacks schools: big business and politics in control, says Californian. (From Springfield [Mass.] Republican. Apr. 4, 1924) Criticism of "The goslings.", PS3537.I85 Z8304 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Sinclair case put up to Birge. (In The Wisconsin state journal. Madison, Wisc. v. 139, no. 32, May 2, 1922. p. [1]) Concerning the question of whether Sinclair would be allowed to speak at the University of Wisconsin., PS3537.I85 Z83044 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair draws big men's meet: noted Socialist says that profit system fails. (In an unidentified newspaper. Beverly Hills, Calif. Mar. 30, 1933), PS3537.I85 Z8305 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair dwells on his hope for production for use via Roosevelt. (In The advisor. Dec. 2, 1936. 2 p.) Mimeographed., PS3537.I85 Z8306 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair endorsed for Nobel Prize. (In The open forum. Los Angeles. v. 9, no. 3, Jan. 16, 1932. p. 2.), PS3537.I85 Z831 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Sinclair for governor — why? (In The voice of youth. Los Angeles: Young Peoples Socialist League. v. 1, no. 3, Oct. 1930. p. [1]) Mimeographed. Supporting Sinclair for governor., PS3537.I85 Z8314 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Sinclair hauled stone and wrote a poem: author of "The jungle" lost three pounds during his workhouse term. (From The New York Tribune. Aug. 3, 1911), PS3537.I85 Z832 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair hurls defi at Chief of Police. (In Los Angeles evening herald. May 17, 1923. ports.) Concerns Sinclair's attack on Chief of Police Oaks., PS3537.I85 Z833 (Box No Box)
- Sinclair loses suit. (In The open forum. Los Angeles. v. 6, no. 26, June 29, 1929. p. 3) Refers to his loss in his $200,000 libel suit against The Rocky Mountain News., PS3537.I85 Z834 2 copies (Box No Box)